{"metadata":{"generator":"Captivate","generatorVersion":"10.0.0","schemaVersion":"","author":"author","title":"","description":"project description","email":"author@company.com","website":"www.company.com","tags":"","thumbnail":"","source":"assets","durationInFrames":1500,"frameRate":30,"totalSlides":11,"width":640,"height":480,"responsive":false,"scalable":true,"launchFile":"index.html"},"contentStructure":[{"id":"Text_Caption_331","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_331","title":"Information Security Awareness Quiz Cybersecurity by the Numbers ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_574","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_574","title":"Take our Security Quiz   to test your knowledge.    Click on Begin to start. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_575","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_575","title":"Brought to you by the Information Security Branch  Office of the Chief Information Officer ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Button_9","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_9","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si21887","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si21901","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"Slide21706","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Text_Caption_331","Text_Caption_574","Text_Caption_575","Button_9","si21887","si21901"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide21706"}}},{"id":"Image_189","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_189","roles":{}},{"id":"si12441","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_338","roles":{}},{"id":"si12349","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_327","title":"1. The cost of cybercrime is growing exponentially, it is estimated to cost how much by 2021?  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12360","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_328","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12364","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_329","title":"$3 trillion ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12360_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"175","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Send your friend a message on social media\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si12382","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_332","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12386","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_333","title":"$1.5 trillion ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12382_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"179","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Contact your friend through phone or in-person\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si20585","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20589","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"$875 billion  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20585_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Don’t worry about it\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si21930","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21934","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"$6 trillion  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21930_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"type the answer here","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si12435","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_337","roles":{}},{"id":"si12459","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_42","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide12483q0","for":"Slide12483q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12473","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_43","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide12483q0","for":"Slide12483q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19347","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide12483q0","for":"Slide12483q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19361","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide12483q0","for":"Slide12483q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19593","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide12483q0","for":"Slide12483q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19606","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide12483q0","for":"Slide12483q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19621","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide12483q0","for":"Slide12483q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19634","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide12483q0","for":"Slide12483q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19649","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide12483q0","for":"Slide12483q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19662","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide12483q0","for":"Slide12483q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19677","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide12483q0","for":"Slide12483q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19690","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide12483q0","for":"Slide12483q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12405","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_334","title":"Correct -  Answer:  D  The amount has grown from $3 trillion in 2015 and, based upon the current statistical trend, will reach $6 trillion by 2021.  Cybercrime will generate more wealth than the worldwide illegal drug trade and will be the highest transfer of wealth for any industry in history.  Press anwhere or click ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12417","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_335","title":"Incorrect -Answer:  D  The amount has grown from $3 trillion in 2015 and, based upon the current statistical trend, will reach $6 trillion by 2021.  Cybercrime will generate more wealth than the worldwide illegal drug trade and will be the highest transfer of wealth for any industry in history.  Press anwhere or click ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12429","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_336","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide12483","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Image_189","si12349","si12364","si12386","si20589","si21934","si12459","si12473","si19347","si19361","si19593","si19606","si19621","si19634","si19649","si19662","si19677","si19690","si12429"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide12483"},"question":{"interactionId":"12329","quizId":458,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"1. The cost of cybercrime is growing exponentially, it is estimated to cost how much by 2021? \r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["D"],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"Image_188","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_188","roles":{}},{"id":"si16169","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_580","roles":{}},{"id":"si16077","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_569","title":"2. In 2017, between just Equifax and Friendfinder, how many user accounts were breached? ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16088","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_570","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16092","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_571","title":"126.7 million ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16088_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"322","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Yes\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si16099","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_572","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16103","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_573","title":"323 million ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16099_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"324","roles":{"answer":{"title":"No\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si21945","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21949","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"559.9 million ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21945_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"type the answer here","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si21960","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21964","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"1.1 billion ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21960_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"type the answer here","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si16163","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_579","roles":{}},{"id":"si16187","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_80","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide16211q1","for":"Slide16211q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16201","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_81","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide16211q1","for":"Slide16211q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19375","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide16211q1","for":"Slide16211q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19389","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide16211q1","for":"Slide16211q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19705","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide16211q1","for":"Slide16211q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19718","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide16211q1","for":"Slide16211q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19733","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide16211q1","for":"Slide16211q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19746","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide16211q1","for":"Slide16211q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19761","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide16211q1","for":"Slide16211q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19774","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide16211q1","for":"Slide16211q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19789","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide16211q1","for":"Slide16211q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19802","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide16211q1","for":"Slide16211q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16133","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_576","title":"Correct - Answer:  C  There were 412 million user accounts stolen from Friendfinder and 147.9 million customers affected by the breach at Equifax for a total of 559.9 million.  The largest known breach of all time was Yahoo with 3 billion records breached in 2016.  Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16145","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_577","title":"Incorrect - Answer:  C  There were 412 million user accounts stolen from Friendfinder and 147.9 million customers affected by the breach at Equifax for a total of 559.9 million.  The largest known breach of all time was Yahoo with 3 billion records breached in 2016.  Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16157","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_578","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide16211","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Image_188","si16077","si16092","si16103","si21949","si21964","si16187","si16201","si19375","si19389","si19705","si19718","si19733","si19746","si19761","si19774","si19789","si19802","si16157"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide16211"},"question":{"interactionId":"16057","quizId":458,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"2. In 2017, between just Equifax and Friendfinder, how many user accounts were breached?\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["C"],"score":{"weight":0,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"Image_177","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_177","roles":{}},{"id":"si16375","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_594","roles":{}},{"id":"si16272","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_581","title":"3.  What is the average cost of a malware attack on a company? ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16283","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_582","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16287","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_583","title":"$3.9 million ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16283_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"329","roles":{"answer":{"title":"$3.9 million\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si16294","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_584","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16298","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_585","title":"$1.3 million  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16294_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"331","roles":{"answer":{"title":"$1.3 million \r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si21319","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21323","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"$7 million ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21319_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"$7 million\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si16369","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_593","roles":{}},{"id":"si16393","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_82","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide16417q2","for":"Slide16417q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16407","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_83","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide16417q2","for":"Slide16417q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19403","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide16417q2","for":"Slide16417q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19417","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide16417q2","for":"Slide16417q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19817","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide16417q2","for":"Slide16417q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19830","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide16417q2","for":"Slide16417q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19845","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide16417q2","for":"Slide16417q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19858","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide16417q2","for":"Slide16417q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19873","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide16417q2","for":"Slide16417q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19886","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide16417q2","for":"Slide16417q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19901","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide16417q2","for":"Slide16417q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19914","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide16417q2","for":"Slide16417q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16339","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_590","title":"Correct - Answer:  A  Current cost of a malware attack is nearly $4 million.  Due to the growing threat and cost of Cyber attacks, companies are spending more than ever to combat their costs.  Cybersecurity spending in 2017 was over $86 billion and is expected to rise to over $1 trillion by next year.  Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16351","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_591","title":"Incorrect - Answer:  A  Current cost of a malware attack is nearly $4 million.  Due to the growing threat and cost of Cyber attacks, companies are spending more than ever to combat their costs.  Cybersecurity spending in 2017 was over $86 billion and is expected to rise to over $1 trillion by next year.  Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16363","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_592","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide16417","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Image_177","si16272","si16287","si16298","si21323","si16393","si16407","si19403","si19417","si19817","si19830","si19845","si19858","si19873","si19886","si19901","si19914","si16363"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide16417"},"question":{"interactionId":"16252","quizId":458,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"3.  What is the average cost of a malware attack on a company?\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["A"],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"Image_178","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_178","roles":{}},{"id":"si16536","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_604","roles":{}},{"id":"si16455","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_595","title":"4.  There is a shortage of cybersecurity workers, their current reported unemployment rate is? ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16466","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_596","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16470","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_597","title":"2% ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16466_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"338","roles":{"answer":{"title":"2%\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si16477","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_598","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16481","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_599","title":"1.5% ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16477_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"340","roles":{"answer":{"title":"1.5%\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si17445","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si17449","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"0% ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si17445_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"0%\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si21990","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21994","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"0.5% ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21990_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"0.5%\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si16530","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_603","roles":{}},{"id":"si16554","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_84","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide16578q3","for":"Slide16578q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16568","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_85","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide16578q3","for":"Slide16578q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19431","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide16578q3","for":"Slide16578q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19445","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide16578q3","for":"Slide16578q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19929","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide16578q3","for":"Slide16578q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19942","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide16578q3","for":"Slide16578q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19957","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide16578q3","for":"Slide16578q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19970","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide16578q3","for":"Slide16578q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19985","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide16578q3","for":"Slide16578q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19998","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide16578q3","for":"Slide16578q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20013","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide16578q3","for":"Slide16578q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20026","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide16578q3","for":"Slide16578q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16500","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_600","title":"Correct -Answer:  C  Unfilled cybersecurity jobs are estimated to reach 3.5 million in the next three years.  If you’re looking for a secure profession, this is it!  Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16512","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_601","title":"Incorrect - Answer:  C  Unfilled cybersecurity jobs are estimated to reach 3.5 million in the next three years.  If you’re looking for a secure profession, this is it!  Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16524","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_602","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide16578","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Image_178","si16455","si16470","si16481","si17449","si21994","si16554","si16568","si19431","si19445","si19929","si19942","si19957","si19970","si19985","si19998","si20013","si20026","si16524"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide16578"},"question":{"interactionId":"16435","quizId":458,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"4.  There is a shortage of cybersecurity workers, their current reported unemployment rate is?\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["C"],"score":{"weight":0,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"Image_179","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_179","roles":{}},{"id":"si16697","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_614","roles":{}},{"id":"si16616","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_605","title":"5. What is the main target of cyber criminals? ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16627","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_606","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16631","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_607","title":"Company networks ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16627_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"343","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Company networks\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si16638","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_608","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16642","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_609","title":"Targeted corporation executives ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16638_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"345","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Targeted corporation executives\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si21353","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21357","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Large retail corporations ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21353_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Large retail corporations\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si21368","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21372","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Internet users ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21368_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Internet users\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si16691","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_613","roles":{}},{"id":"si16715","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_86","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide16739q4","for":"Slide16739q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16729","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_87","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide16739q4","for":"Slide16739q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19459","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide16739q4","for":"Slide16739q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19473","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide16739q4","for":"Slide16739q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20041","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide16739q4","for":"Slide16739q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20054","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide16739q4","for":"Slide16739q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20069","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide16739q4","for":"Slide16739q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20082","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide16739q4","for":"Slide16739q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20097","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide16739q4","for":"Slide16739q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20110","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide16739q4","for":"Slide16739q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20125","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide16739q4","for":"Slide16739q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20138","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide16739q4","for":"Slide16739q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16661","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_610","title":"Correct - Answer:  D  Due to the large number of internet users, the ‘human attack surface’ has moved ahead of machines as the top target for cybercrime.  There were nearly 4 billion internet users in 2017 (51% of the world population) and it is expected to grow to 6 billion users (75% of projected population) by 2021.  Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16673","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_611","title":"Incorrect - Answer:  D  Due to the large number of internet users, the ‘human attack surface’ has moved ahead of machines as the top target for cybercrime.  There were nearly 4 billion internet users in 2017 (51% of the world population) and it is expected to grow to 6 billion users (75% of projected population) by 2021.  Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16685","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_612","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide16739","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Image_179","si16616","si16631","si16642","si21357","si21372","si16715","si16729","si19459","si19473","si20041","si20054","si20069","si20082","si20097","si20110","si20125","si20138","si16685"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide16739"},"question":{"interactionId":"16596","quizId":458,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"5. What is the main target of cyber criminals?\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["D"],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"Image_180","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_180","roles":{}},{"id":"si16858","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_624","roles":{}},{"id":"si16777","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_615","title":"6.  What is the most cyber-attacked industry? ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16788","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_616","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16792","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_617","title":"Banks ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16788_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Banks\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si16799","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_618","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16803","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_619","title":"Healthcare ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16799_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Healthcare\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si22005","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22009","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Retail ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22005_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Retail\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si22020","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22024","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Government ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22020_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Government\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si16852","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_623","roles":{}},{"id":"si16876","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_88","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide16900q5","for":"Slide16900q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16890","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_89","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide16900q5","for":"Slide16900q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19487","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide16900q5","for":"Slide16900q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19501","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide16900q5","for":"Slide16900q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20153","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide16900q5","for":"Slide16900q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20166","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide16900q5","for":"Slide16900q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20181","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide16900q5","for":"Slide16900q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20194","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide16900q5","for":"Slide16900q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20209","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide16900q5","for":"Slide16900q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20222","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide16900q5","for":"Slide16900q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20237","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide16900q5","for":"Slide16900q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20250","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide16900q5","for":"Slide16900q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16846","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_622","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21378","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Correct - Answer:  B  Modern healthcare uses a multitude of connected devices and technology allowing hackers to find multiple points of entry into their network, making it an easy target.  Because they are considered part of the critical infrastructure, services must remain available.   Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21382","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Incorrect - Answer:  B  Modern healthcare uses a multitude of connected devices and technology allowing hackers to find multiple points of entry into their network, making it an easy target.  Because they are considered part of the critical infrastructure, services must remain available.   Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide16900","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Image_180","si16777","si16792","si16803","si22009","si22024","si16876","si16890","si19487","si19501","si20153","si20166","si20181","si20194","si20209","si20222","si20237","si20250","si16846"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide16900"},"question":{"interactionId":"16757","quizId":458,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"6.  What is the most cyber-attacked industry?\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["B"],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"Image_181","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_181","roles":{}},{"id":"si17049","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_636","roles":{}},{"id":"si16957","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_625","title":"7.  The global ‘attack surface’ is growing with Internet of Things devices, self-driving cars and a growing number of people online (‘human attack surface’) but increased data is the most tempting target for hackers.  True or False? ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16968","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_626","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16972","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_627","title":"True ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16968_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"True\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si16979","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_628","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16983","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_629","title":"False ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16979_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"False\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si17043","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_635","roles":{}},{"id":"si17067","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_90","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide17091q6","for":"Slide17091q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si17081","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_91","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide17091q6","for":"Slide17091q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19515","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide17091q6","for":"Slide17091q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19529","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide17091q6","for":"Slide17091q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20265","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide17091q6","for":"Slide17091q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20278","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide17091q6","for":"Slide17091q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20293","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide17091q6","for":"Slide17091q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20306","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide17091q6","for":"Slide17091q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20321","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide17091q6","for":"Slide17091q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20334","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide17091q6","for":"Slide17091q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20349","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide17091q6","for":"Slide17091q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20362","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide17091q6","for":"Slide17091q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si17013","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_632","title":"Correct - Answer:  A  The main target for cybercriminals is the internet and the main target on the internet is data.  The amount of data is estimated to grow 50 times in the next two years.  Hundreds of billions of new lines of code each year exposes billions of vulnerabilities to be exploited.  Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si17025","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_633","title":"Incorrect - Answer:  A  The main target for cybercriminals is the internet and the main target on the internet is data.  The amount of data is estimated to grow 50 times in the next two years.  Hundreds of billions of new lines of code each year exposes billions of vulnerabilities to be exploited.  Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si17037","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_634","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide17091","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Image_181","si16957","si16972","si16983","si17067","si17081","si19515","si19529","si20265","si20278","si20293","si20306","si20321","si20334","si20349","si20362","si17037"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide17091"},"question":{"interactionId":"16937","quizId":458,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"7.  The global ‘attack surface’ is growing with Internet of Things devices, self-driving cars and a growing number of people online (‘human attack surface’) but increased data is the most tempting target for hackers.  True or False?\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["A"],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"Image_182","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_182","roles":{}},{"id":"si17225","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_648","roles":{}},{"id":"si17133","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_637","title":"8.  Who said, “Cyber attacks are the number one problem with mankind, even worse than nuclear weapons”? ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si17144","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_638","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si17148","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_639","title":"Warren Buffet ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si17144_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"360","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Warren Buffet\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si17155","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_640","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si17159","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_641","title":"Ginni Rometty, IBM CEO ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si17155_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"362","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Ginni Rometty, IBM CEO\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si21580","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21584","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Elon Musk, Tesla CEO ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21580_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Elon Musk, Tesla CEO\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si21595","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21599","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Stephen Hawking ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21595_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Stephen Hawking\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si17219","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_647","roles":{}},{"id":"si17243","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_92","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide17267q7","for":"Slide17267q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si17257","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_93","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide17267q7","for":"Slide17267q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19543","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide17267q7","for":"Slide17267q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19557","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide17267q7","for":"Slide17267q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20377","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide17267q7","for":"Slide17267q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20390","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide17267q7","for":"Slide17267q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20405","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide17267q7","for":"Slide17267q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20418","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide17267q7","for":"Slide17267q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20433","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide17267q7","for":"Slide17267q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20446","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide17267q7","for":"Slide17267q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20461","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide17267q7","for":"Slide17267q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20474","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide17267q7","for":"Slide17267q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si17189","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_644","title":"Correct -  Answer:  A  The statement was made by Warren Buffet at Berkshire Hathaway’s 2017 annual shareholder’s meeting.  Ginni Rometty of IBM stated in 2015 that “Cybercrime is the greatest threat to every company in the world”.  Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si17201","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_645","title":"Incorrect - Answer:  A  The statement was made by Warren Buffet at Berkshire Hathaway’s 2017 annual shareholder’s meeting.  Ginni Rometty of IBM stated in 2015 that “Cybercrime is the greatest threat to every company in the world”.  Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si17213","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_646","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide17267","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Image_182","si17133","si17148","si17159","si21584","si21599","si17243","si17257","si19543","si19557","si20377","si20390","si20405","si20418","si20433","si20446","si20461","si20474","si17213"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide17267"},"question":{"interactionId":"17113","quizId":458,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"8.  Who said, “Cyber attacks are the number one problem with mankind, even worse than nuclear weapons”?\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["A"],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"Image_185","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_185","roles":{}},{"id":"Text_Caption_107","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_107","title":"Quiz Results ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6059","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si6083","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si6091","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si6055","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"You Scored: ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6079","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Total Questions: ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6087","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Accuracy: ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6103","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si6107","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Continue ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"continue","question":"","for":""},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6121","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Review Quiz ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"review","question":"","for":""},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20489","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Continue ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"continue","question":"","for":""},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20502","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Continue ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"continue","question":"","for":""},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20517","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Review Quiz ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"review","question":"","for":""},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20530","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Review Quiz ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"review","question":"","for":""},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide6038","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":[],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide6038"}}},{"id":"si6231","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Image_186","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_186","roles":{}},{"id":"Button_4","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_4","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si19054","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si19068","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"SmartShape_9","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_9","title":" Stay Current With Information Security By Subscribing to the:   Weekly Security News Digest ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_298","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_298","title":"Thank you for taking the quiz.  To exit the quiz, close the browser window. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide6219","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si6231","Image_186","Button_4","si19054","si19068","SmartShape_9","Text_Caption_298"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":600},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide6219"}}},{"id":"Pool502","class":"pool","roles":{"pool":{"id":502,"name":"Pool1","questions":[]}}},{"id":"October2018Quiz","class":"project","title":"October2018Quiz","children":["Slide21706","Slide12483","Slide16211","Slide16417","Slide16578","Slide16739","Slide16900","Slide17091","Slide17267","Slide6038","Slide6219"],"roles":{"quiz":{"id":458,"branched":false,"submitAll":false,"review":true,"questions":["Slide12483q0","Slide16211q1","Slide16417q2","Slide16578q3","Slide16739q4","Slide16900q5","Slide17091q6","Slide17267q7"],"minScore":0,"maxScore":60,"passScore":48}}}],"contentSettings":{"global":{"branchAware":false},"toc":{"enabled":false},"playbar":{"enabled":true,"cc":false,"playPause":true,"back":true,"forward":true,"rewind":true,"close":true,"mute":true,"progressBar":true}},"contentReporting":{"CCCriteria":"quiz","CCData":{"quizData":"quiz_passed"},"SCCriteria":"quiz","SCData":{"quizData":"quiz_passed"},"exitNormalIfCompleted":false},"toc":[{"id":"Slide21706","title":"Slide 1"},{"id":"Slide12483","title":"Slide 2"},{"id":"Slide16211","title":"Slide 3"},{"id":"Slide16417","title":"Slide 4"},{"id":"Slide16578","title":"Slide 5"},{"id":"Slide16739","title":"Slide 6"},{"id":"Slide16900","title":"Slide 7"},{"id":"Slide17091","title":"Slide 8"},{"id":"Slide17267","title":"Slide 9"},{"id":"Slide6038","title":"Slide 10"},{"id":"Slide6219","title":"Slide 11"}]}